

### Nurhafizatul Ni'mah Haji Ahmad Sanuddin

naeemahmds@gmail.com

+6737113629

No. 89, Spg. 89, Jln. Dua Berdikari, Kg. Kupang Tutong, Bandar Seri Begawan, Brunei

∂ **∀** ei

linkedin.com/in/hafizaahmads in

Computer Science graduate pursuing an entry-level position, related to my field of specialization particularly in Information Technology (IT), to seize any opportunity for meaningful personal development in order to professionally progress in the career and in a productive working environment of an organization, and simultaneously contributing and serving to the workplace.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Data Centre (DC) Infrastructure Intern Baiduri Bank

08/2016 - 10/2016

Kiarong, Bandar Seri Begawan

- Tasks:
- Practical experience as a DC Server and Network Administrator.
- IT hands-on task: proper installation and disassembly of Baiduri network server device from and into the server rack, routing and switching equipment.
- Updating the list of the shared folder and security access permission detail by accessing the server; sending an enquiry email to every member of the folder to confirm the primary and secondary owner.
- Learnt Baiduri Internal Network system operation, Data Centre Manual and the role of Data Centre Infrastructure and Group Technology Department; made a short descriptive report on Baiduri Network based on Telbru Metro Ethernet solution diagram.
- Attended IT-related training and meeting with Baiduri vendors.

Contact: Royne Kong (Supervisor) -

Tel : 2268300 ext. 8338 Émail : Royne@baiduri.com.bn

### Resource & Social Marketing Intern

Health Promotion Centre

01/2016 - 04/2016

Berakas, Bandar Seri Begawan

- Tasks:
- Took part in promoting health information to the public by participating in health events; roadshows, exhibition, forums, symposium and fitness programs.
- Implemented desktop database using Microsoft Access for the purpose of managing the resource caollections into categories.
- Demonstrated the resource collection management completed desktop database to RSM team.
- Cooperated with the Resource Centre team and staff in charged in any general task concerning the department.

Contact: Siti Munawwarah Awang Tarif (Supervisor) – Tel : 2385800 ext. 243 Fax : 2384223 Email : munawwarah.tarif@moh.gov.bn

#### **LANGUAGES**

Malay Native or Bilingual Proficiency English

Full Professional Proficiency

#### **EDUCATION**

# O Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Universiti Brunei Darussalam

01/2014 - 08/2018

Final Year Project & Courses:

- Interactive Graphical User Interface using LabVIEW (FYP).
- Programming Fundamental.
- **-** Software Engineering.
- Internet Application Development.
- Computer System and Network.
- Operating systems.
- System Analysis and Design.
- Database Design.

#### **TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE & SKILLS**

#### Programming Language & Code

Java, Javascript, HTML CSS codes (Front-end Web Development & Design), G (visual dataflow programming), Little experience with C and PHP.

#### Operating System/Platform

Windows, macOS & Linux OS, Microsoft Office (Words, Excel, Access, Powerpoint), Google Drive/Docs/Sheet, LabVIEW, SPSS

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

			1	1	
Teamwork	i			•	
Active Listening	-				
Time Management	ı				
Oral & Written Communication	ı				
Self-motivation					
Problem Solving	Ī				
Leadership					
	_	$\overline{}$			
Presentation & Public	/ I				_
Speaking			\	///	

#### **INTERESTS**

Self-improvement Community Involvement

Travelling Cooking Mathematics Science

Playing piano Reading news & articles

#### **REFERENCES**

Norafizah Marjuki (Senior Data Centre Officer)

Contact: Norafizah@baiduri.com.bn - 2268300 ext. 8847

Royne Kong (Data Infrastructure, System and Network Admin)

Contact: Royne@baiduri.com.bn - 2268300 ext. 8338

Siti Nurbazilah Junaidi (Data Centre Librarian Officer)

Contact: Nur.bazilah@baiduri.com.bn - 2268300 ext. 8889

Siti Munawwarah Awg Tarif (Health Education Officer)

Contact: munawwarah.tarif@moh.gov.bn - 2385800 ext. 243